Contact

mtartaro@northwell.edu

www.linkedin.com/in/michael-j-tartaro-5737131b (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service
Healthcare
Healthcare Information Technology

Michael J Tartaro

Asst Nurse Manager at Northwell health Babylon, New York

Summary

Experienced Nurse Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Specializing in Psychiatry and most recently in Geriatric Psychiatry. Strong healthcare services professional with a BSN focused in Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing from State University of New York College at Plattsburgh.

Experience

Northwell Health
Asst Nurse Manager
February 2010 - Present (10 years 6 months)
Zucker-Hillside Hospital

Zucker hillside hospital

NYC Health + Hospitals
Assistant Director/Manager
April 2005 - December 2009 (4 years 9 months)
Bellevue Hospital

Northwell Health Staff RN November 1998 - March 2005 (6 years 5 months) Zucker-Hillside Hospital

Education

State University of New York College at Plattsburgh BSN, Registered Nursing, Nursing Administration, Nursing Research and Clinical Nursing